lamaloli.com 2019-04-08

# Privacy Policy

**Effective Date: 25.05.2018**

**GBG Europe  
**

**Lamaloli Website Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy sets out how Lamaloli GmbH uses and protects any personal data that you provide to us when you use this website (www.Lamaloli.com and www.wholesale.lamaloli.com) (“Website”). Lamaloli GmbH is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this Website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Lamaloli GmbH may change this Privacy Policy from time to time by updating this page. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to this Privacy Policy. 

Lamaloli GmbH is the controller of your personal data via our Website.  

__________

**INDEX**

**1\. HOW IS YOUR PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED**

**2\. PURPOSES FOR PROCESSING YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

**3\. MARKETING**

**4\. SHARING YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

**5\. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS**

**6\. DATA RETENTION**

**7\. YOUR RIGHTS**

**1\. HOW IS YOUR PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED**

We may process your personal data when you submit it to us in the following ways: 

  * Communications via our Website: We collect personal data when you provide it to us through communications via our Website. This includes where you have contacted us through the channels listed on the “Contact Us” page on our Website and similar situations in which you have chosen to provide the information to us, including for customer services support. 
  * Goods or services you request: Where you request a good or service from us, we will collect your personal data in order to process your request and otherwise contact you following a purchase. 
  * Automated technologies or interactions. As you interact with our Website, we may automatically collect technical data about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns. We collect this personal data by using cookies, server logs and other similar technologies. Please see our cookie policy [https://wholesale.lamaloli.com/en/cookie-policy/] for further details.
  * Third parties or publicly available sources. We may receive personal data about you from various third parties and public sources, for example providers of technical, payment and delivery services. 

The type of personal data we may collect includes identity data (including name and title), contact data (including postal address, email address and telephone numbers), financial data (including bank account and payment card details), transaction data (details of products and services you have purchased from us) and profile data (including your interests, preferences, feedback and survey responses). 

**2\. PURPOSES FOR PROCESSING YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

We process any personal data you provide to us to enable us to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you, to ensure compliance with local legal and regulatory requirements and for the purposes of our legitimate business interests, including: 

  * to enable us to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us; 
  * to enable us to respond to an enquiry or other request you make when you contact us via our Website, including for customer services support; 
  * to notify you about changes to our service; to enable us to issue a notice or corrective action to you in relation to any of our products or services, if required; 
  * to better understand how you interact with our Website, including its functionality and features, and ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner; and to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about and we feel may interest you, as described in the “Marketing” section below.

**3\. MARKETING**

We may contact you to provide you with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale or negotiations of a sale to you. You may be contacted by us, Global Brands Group affiliated companies, or by one of our selected partners, in each case where you have consented to receive these communications.

You may opt out of receiving our marketing communications at any time by contacting us at support@lamaloli.com or by using the unsubscribe link in any of our communications.

We will continue to contact you for non-marketing related purposes where we need to issue a field corrective or safety notice, or to where we need to send certain information to you under a legal, regulatory, or ethical requirement. 

**4\. SHARING YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

We may share your personal data with:

  * other companies within the Global Brands Group; 
  * our selected commercial partners and sponsors where you have chosen to participate in surveys, opinion groups or other marketing-related initiatives relating to your use of our goods and services; 
  * a prospective seller or buyer in the event of a sale or purchase of any Global Brands Group business or asset so that the buyer can continue to provide you with information and services; 
  * our service providers that we engage to provide services for us. Where we provide your personal data to third party services providers, they are required to keep your personal data confidential and secure, and must only use your personal data as instructed by us; and 
  * our distributors, business partners, or other service providers, including for marketing purposes or where you have chosen to share your personal data through various features and functionality provided via our Website. 

We may also disclose your personal data where required to respond to authorised requests from government authorities or where required by law. Where we are required by law, we may also disclose your personal data where it is necessary to enforce or apply this Privacy Policy or other agreements, to investigate or protect the rights, property or safety of Lamaloli GmbH and other companies within the Global Brands Group, our products and services and our customers, distributors or business partners or to prevent or take action regarding illegal activities or fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person or as evidence in litigation. 

**5\. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS**

We may share your personal data within the Global Brands Group. If you are located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), this will involve transferring your data outside the EEA. 

Many of our external third parties are based outside the EEA so their processing of your personal data will involve a transfer of data outside the EEA. Whenever we transfer your personal data outside of the EEA, we ensure a similar degree of protection is afforded to it by ensuring at least one of the following safeguards is implemented: 

  * We will only transfer your personal data to countries that have been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for personal data by the European Commission. For further details, see European Commission: Adequacy of the protection of personal data in non-EU countries. 
  * Where we use certain service providers, we may use specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in Europe. For further details, see European Commission: Model contracts for the transfer of personal data to third countries. 
  * Where we use providers based in the US, we may transfer data to them if they are part of the Privacy Shield which requires them to provide similar protection to personal data shared between the Europe and the US. For further details, see European Commission: EU-US Privacy Shield. 

For further information on the specific mechanism used by us when transferring your personal data outside of the EEA, please send your request to support@lamaloli.com. We will process any request in line with any local laws and our policies and procedures. 

**6\. DATA RETENTION**

We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements. 

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements. 

**7\. YOUR RIGHTS**

You may inform us of any changes in your personal data, and in accordance with our obligations under applicable data protection laws we will update or delete your personal data accordingly. 

EEA residents: You may have the right to: request (a) access the to your personal data we hold about you; (b) request we correct any inaccurate personal data we hold about you; (c) request we delete any personal data we hold about you; (d) restrict the processing of personal data we hold about you; (e) object to the processing of personal data we hold about you; and/or (f) receive any personal data we hold about you in a structured and commonly used machine-readable format or have such personal information transmitted to another company. 

We may ask you for additional information to confirm your identity and for security purposes, before disclosing information requested to you. 

To exercise any of your rights in connection with your personal data, please contact support@lamaloli.com. We will process any request in line with any local laws and our policies and procedures. If you are located in the EEA, you have the right to lodge a complaint about how we process your personal data with the supervisory authority in your country. 

**8\. CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about the processing of personal data via this Website, please contact us by email at support@lamaloli.com. If you contact us, we will do our utmost best to address any concerns you may have about our processing of your personal data.
